http://www.braintrauma.org/pages/privacy-policy

Partcipate
What are you looking for?
Search Now
Information About UsBrain Trauma Foundation, (“BTF”, “we”, “our”, “us”), respects the privacy rights of its users (“you”, “your”, “yours”) and recognizes the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We provide this statement (the “Privacy Policy”) to help you to understand what we do with any personal information that we obtain from you. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, store and use the information that you provide to us.By providing your personal information to us, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and agree that we may collect, use and disclose your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Terms and Conditions, which govern, in general, your use of braintrauma.org, including any subdomains, any embedded code or objects, and any web services (collectively, “Site”). Hereinafter, BTF shall mean BTF and the officers, directors, shareholders, employees, agents, parents, subsidiaries and affiliates of BTF.We will use your information obtained through the Site only for the purposes set out below. This Privacy Policy does not govern our collection or use of data about you not obtained through the Site.Please exit the Site immediately if you do not accept this Privacy Policy or are accessing the Site in a country or other location where use of the Site is not permitted.We may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We recommend that you regularly check this page to ensure that you have read the most recent version.Changes to the Privacy Policy are noted here:Date last revised: 2010-02-24Types of Information CollectedThe following is provided by BTF to enable our online visitors to be fully informed of our Privacy Policy. The Site collects certain information (“Personal Information”) when you interact with the Site, including data that can be used to identify an individual, as defined by applicable law. The Site may also collect data that does not identify you specifically. The following is a list of data that we may collect and process about you:Information that you provide by filling out forms on the Site. This includes information you provide when you register to use the Site; subscribe to any services offered on the Site including but not limited to interactive services (such as blogs, chat rooms, message boards, or other user forums); complete a survey; or report a problem with the Site;Your correct date of birth, which we may require that you submit accurately to ensure that you do not access the Site if you are not of a legal age to purchase items offered for sale on the Site;Any information you may provide when you contact us or send us a correspondence;Details of any transactions you carry out through the Site including the placement of any orders by you; andDetails of your visits to the Site including, but not limited to, your computer’s IP address, password information, page interaction information, traffic data, location data, weblogs, and other data about the resources that you access.We may change registration requirements from time to time. When you register and create an account, you are required to provide information about yourself that is true, accurate, current and complete in all respects. Any information you provide on the Site is also governed by our Privacy Policy.HOW WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM YOU?BTF collects Personal Information in several ways when you place an order or register for a service offered by BTF. If an order is placed with us, we need to hold Personal Information including your name, email address, phone numbers, home address, shipping and credit card billing address(es) so that we can process and fulfill your order. We only save credit card information for those users that have registered at the Site. Saved card details will never be shared with third parties and will only be used to process your order, using our payment partner’s systems. Additionally we may also obtain information as a result of authentication or identity checks. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number. This number may be given to our courier for delivery services. These details allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order.USE OF COOKIES ON OUR WEBSITEIn common with many websites, we use “cookies” to help us gather and store information about visitors to our Site. A cookie is a small data file that our server sends to your browser when you visit the Site. The use of cookies helps us provide certain functionality. You can delete cookies at any time or you can set your browser to reject or disable cookies. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to the Site.We may use information from cookies for the following purposes:Traffic monitoring, for example, the IP address from which you access the Site, the type of browser and operating system used to access the site, the date and time of your access to the site, the pages you visit, and the Internet address of the website from which you accessed our Site;To recognize repeat visitors for statistical/analytical purposes; orAnonymous tracking of interaction with online advertising, for example, to monitor the number of times that a banner ad is displayed and the number of times it is clicked.We may connect the information that we collect through cookies with other Personal Information that you provide to us. Such purposes are:To customize or personalize your experience of the Site; for example, so that we can greet you on the site by name;For transactional purposes, such as credit card sales; orTo monitor your use of the Site in order to make our communications with you as relevant as possible; for example, by sending you email communications relevant to the parts of the Site that you visit most often or by letting you know about features of the Site that you have not accessed previously.We may compile and report to third parties (such as advertisers) aggregate statistics about our users in terms of numbers, traffic patterns and related site information.HOW PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE USED, INCLUDING ANYONE IT MIGHT BE SHARED WITHBTF may use your Personal Information for the processing of orders, payments and to provide you with a personalized shopping experience. We will also use your details to fulfill and deliver your orders and manage your account. Your Personal Information may also be checked with credit agencies to prevent fraud. Where there is a legal obligation to do so, we may disclose your information to any relevant regulatory body.However, if you choose to (opt-in) receive our emails from time-to-time we will use the information you provide to promote the products and services of our business partners and affiliates, or to invite you to make a donation. We do collate statistical information about Site traffic, sales and other commercial information which we may pass on to trusted third parties but these statistics do not include any information which can identify you personally. You may, at any time, opt-out of receiving any communication from us, except those communications related individual transactions initiated by you, such as a purchase or donation.Finally, we may use your Personal Information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, together with non-personal data to monitor user patterns so we can consistently improve our site design to better meet our visitors’ needs.In addition to disclosures identified in the purposes above, from time to time we may disclose Personal Information toour service providers and subcontractors, including our affiliates, retained to perform functions on our behalf or to provide services to us, such as warehousing and delivery; marketing and advertising; data processing; software development; website hosting and management; information technology and office services; legal, accounting, audit and other professional service providers; and further provided such service provider does not collect, use or disclose the Personal Information for any purpose other than to perform such functions or to provide services to us or as otherwise required by law;Unaffiliated service providers with whom BTF may subcontract, including website hosting companies, fulfillment companies and other third party service providers;If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to: comply with any legal or regulatory obligation; respond to inquiries or requests from public authority; enforce or apply the BTF Terms of Use and other agreements; permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; or protect the rights, property, safety or security of BTF, our employees, agents, contractors, customers, the visitors of the Site or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.OPT-IN AND OPT-OUT PROVISIONSWhen you register, we will provide a link to the Privacy Policy and consent button for the collection of your personal data.BTF does not disclose any Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes (“Remarketing”) unless the you opt-in for Remarketing. Any such option to opt-in is accompanied by a description of what and how and to whom your information will be Remarketed. In addition, each communication you receive from BTF provides you the option to opt-out of Remarketing. At all times, you can opt-out of Remarketing by logging into your account and opt-out of Remarketing.HOW YOU CAN ACCESS AND, IF NECESSARY, CHANGE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION BRAIN TRUST FOUNDATION MAINTAINSIf for any reason you are concerned that the Personal Information held by BTF is not correct, please modify your Personal Information by logging in to your account and updating your Personal Information. If you prefer, you may contact us by email at infogroup@braintrauma.org and we will modify your Personal Information.SAFEGUARDING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATIONBTF uses VeriSign issued and certified Secure Socket Layer Certificates for the encryption and protection of your personal and financial information.Data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the United States. Data we collect may also be processed by staff operating outside the US who work for us or for one of our suppliers or service providers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storage or processing. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a user identification code, password or any other piece of information as a part of a registration scheme or a security procedure to enable you to access certain parts of the Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. BTF is not liable to you for any use of the Site or purchase of any merchandise as a result of any use by anyone other than you of your password or account information.We will only collect personally identifiable information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve you in view of our legitimate business purposes as set out above, and we will use our best endeavors to maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided us with. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third party business partners’ to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that Personal Information. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of the data you transmit to the Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use reasonable efforts to try to prevent unauthorized access.In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email.LINKSThe Site may contain links or references to other websites outside of our control. Links to other websites may use our Site logo or style as a result of a co-branding agreement. These websites may send their own cookies to you and may collect data and make use of that data in ways that this Site would not. We have no control over these websites, our Privacy Policy does not apply to these sites, and BTF is not responsible nor liable for any aspect of another site nor any damages caused by another site.WHERE AND HOW TO ASK QUESTIONS OR FILE COMPLAINTSIf you require further information about our Privacy Policy, please go to the help section of the Site where frequently asked questions (FAQ’s) are answered. If you require more information please go to the Contact Us section of the Site and send an email to the relevant BTF department. If you wish to talk to a BTF service team representative please email infogroup@braintrauma.org.
Concussion
Guidelines
Research
News
About
Contact
Donate
Careers
